alertpay.com 2006-06-21

# AlertPay.com-My Way To Pay

**OVERVIEW**

AlertPay takes the privacy of your personal information very seriously and will use your information only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information or a list of our customers to third parties. If you are a registered AlertPay user, your name, e-mail address, and whether you are verified are displayed to other AlertPay customers whom you have paid or who are attempting to pay you through AlertPay. If you are a Business account holder, we will also display to other AlertPay customers your web site address (URL). 

Please note, your credit card number, bank account and other financial information will NEVER be revealed to anyone whom you have paid or who has paid you through AlertPay. If you are buying goods or services and paying through AlertPay, the seller of the goods or services may request that you provide a mailing address that AlertPay has verified through its verification status. If you do not provide the information, the seller may choose not to accept your AlertPay payment and not to complete the transaction. 

By accepting the Privacy Policy and User Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. 

* * *

**REQUIRED INFORMATION**

To open a AlertPay account, you must provide your name, address, phone number, and e-mail address. We also ask you to create two different security questions to answer to protect your account. This required information is necessary for us to process transactions, issue a new password if you forget or lose your password, protect you against account fraud, and to contact you should the need arise in administering your account. We also require a secondary password for additional security. 

* * *

**VERIFICATION**

In order to become an AlertPay Verified member, we will request you submit additional information by email and/or postal mail (such as copies of your drivers' license, credit card statement, and/or a recent utility bill or other information linking you to the applicable address). Verification increases the security of the AlertPay network. 

* * *

**INTERNAL USE OF INFORMATION**

We collect, store and process your personal information on servers located in Canada. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect our servers 24 hours a day. We use the information we collect about you in order to provide our services and process your transactions and to provide proper customer service. 

We give access to individually identifiable information about our users only to those employees who require it to fulfill customer service requests. Your complete banking or credit card information is never exposed, and at most only your last 4 digits will be visible for verification purposes. All financial data is stored in encrypted format. 

* * *

**INFORMATION SECURITY**

AlertPay is committed to handling your customer information with high standards of information security. Your credit card and bank account information are stored only in encrypted form on computers that are not connected to the Internet. When your information is being transferred over the internet, 128 bit SSL encryption is used to ensure your sensitive data is not legible by anyone on the internet. We restrict access to your personally identifiable information to only employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your information. 

* * *

**PRIVACY ISSUES**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, AlertPay's information practices, or your dealings with AlertPay, you can contact us through the following means: 

  * Our Support page
  * Call us at:  (514)748-5774  Monday through Friday between 10am and 5pm EST 
  * Write to us: AlertPay, 5200 De La Savane, Suite 220, Montreal, Quebec H4P-2M8
